<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by Radio UserLand v8.0.8 on Fri, 17 Sep 2004 00:36:48 GMT -->
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Jeremy Allaire&apos;s Radio </title>
		<link>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/</link>
		<description>An exploration of media, communications and applications over the Internet.</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<copyright>Copyright 2004 Jeremy Allaire</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2004 00:36:48 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss</docs>
		<generator>Radio UserLand v8.0.8</generator>
		<managingEditor>jer_allaire@yahoo.com</managingEditor>
		<webMaster>jer_allaire@yahoo.com</webMaster>
		<category domain="http://www.weblogs.com/rssUpdates/changes.xml">rssUpdates</category> 
		<skipHours>
			<hour>1</hour>
			<hour>2</hour>
			<hour>3</hour>
			<hour>4</hour>
			<hour>5</hour>
			<hour>17</hour>
			<hour>23</hour>
			<hour>0</hour>
			</skipHours>
		<cloud domain="radio.xmlstoragesystem.com" port="80" path="/RPC2" registerProcedure="xmlStorageSystem.rssPleaseNotify" protocol="xml-rpc"/>
		<ttl>60</ttl>
		<item>
			<title>Paying for Online Media</title>
			<link>http://www.paidcontent.org/contentnext/jeremy_allaire/consumer_evolution_a.php</link>
			<description>&lt;A href=&quot;http://www.paidcontent.org/contentnext/jeremy_allaire/consumer_evolution_a.php&quot;&gt;Thoughts on the economic basis of and consumer interests&lt;/A&gt; around pay media on the Internet.</description>
			<guid>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/2004/09/16.html#a294</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2004 00:36:48 GMT</pubDate>
			<comments>http://radiocomments.userland.com/comments?u=113297&amp;amp;p=294&amp;amp;link=http%3A%2F%2Fradio.weblogs.com%2F0113297%2F2004%2F09%2F16.html%23a294</comments>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bandwidth vs Storage</title>
			<link>http://www.paidcontent.org/contentnext/jeremy_allaire/bandwidth_versus_sto.php</link>
			<description>&lt;P&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;http://www.paidcontent.org/contentnext/jeremy_allaire/bandwidth_versus_sto.php&quot;&gt;My discussion on the bandwidth versus storage versus quality debate&lt;/A&gt; on PaidContent.org.&lt;/P&gt;</description>
			<guid>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/2004/09/16.html#a293</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2004 14:54:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<comments>http://radiocomments.userland.com/comments?u=113297&amp;amp;p=293&amp;amp;link=http%3A%2F%2Fradio.weblogs.com%2F0113297%2F2004%2F09%2F16.html%23a293</comments>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Flashing Mobile Content</title>
			<link>http://www.paidcontent.org/contentnext/flashing_mobile_cont.php</link>
			<description>&lt;A href=&quot;http://www.paidcontent.org/contentnext/flashing_mobile_cont.php&quot;&gt;Comments on emergence of Flash&lt;/A&gt; as a mobile format on PaidContent.org</description>
			<guid>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/2004/09/14.html#a292</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2004 18:31:57 GMT</pubDate>
			<comments>http://radiocomments.userland.com/comments?u=113297&amp;amp;p=292&amp;amp;link=http%3A%2F%2Fradio.weblogs.com%2F0113297%2F2004%2F09%2F14.html%23a292</comments>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Comments on TiVo / NetFlix  deal</title>
			<link>http://www.paidcontent.org/contentnext/jeremy_allaire/tivoflixing_the_vide.php</link>
			<description>&lt;A href=&quot;http://www.paidcontent.org/contentnext/jeremy_allaire/tivoflixing_the_vide.php&quot;&gt;TivoFlixing&lt;/A&gt; the Video world....</description>
			<guid>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/2004/09/13.html#a291</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2004 02:38:42 GMT</pubDate>
			<comments>http://radiocomments.userland.com/comments?u=113297&amp;amp;p=291&amp;amp;link=http%3A%2F%2Fradio.weblogs.com%2F0113297%2F2004%2F09%2F13.html%23a291</comments>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Internet of Video</title>
			<link>http://www.paidcontent.org/contentnext/jeremy_allaire/the_internet_of_vide.php</link>
			<description>&lt;P&gt;Guest posting on PaidContent.org ... some thoughts on emerging opportunities in video on the Internet.&lt;/P&gt;</description>
			<guid>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/2004/09/13.html#a290</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2004 02:37:45 GMT</pubDate>
			<comments>http://radiocomments.userland.com/comments?u=113297&amp;amp;p=290&amp;amp;link=http%3A%2F%2Fradio.weblogs.com%2F0113297%2F2004%2F09%2F13.html%23a290</comments>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Guest Blogging on PaidContent.org</title>
			<link>http://www.paidcontent.org/contentnext/</link>
			<description>I&apos;m pleased to be a &lt;A href=&quot;http://www.paidcontent.org/contentnext/&quot;&gt;guest blogger / interview on Rafat Ali&apos;s PaidContent.org&lt;/A&gt;, among my favorite spots on the Web for my daily dose of digital media.&amp;nbsp; Rafat has launched the &lt;A href=&quot;http://www.paidcontent.org/contentnext/&quot;&gt;ContentNext series&lt;/A&gt; of guest blogs on his site.&amp;nbsp; I&apos;ll be writing on a variety of topics including Internet video, the role of Flash on mobile, TiVo/NetFlix deal, and several other topics during this week.&amp;nbsp; I&apos;ll also cross-link to each of my main posts.</description>
			<guid>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/2004/09/13.html#a289</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2004 02:36:54 GMT</pubDate>
			<comments>http://radiocomments.userland.com/comments?u=113297&amp;amp;p=289&amp;amp;link=http%3A%2F%2Fradio.weblogs.com%2F0113297%2F2004%2F09%2F13.html%23a289</comments>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Distracted...by TV</title>
			<link>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/2004/04/20.html#a288</link>
			<description>I&apos;ve been quite distracted over the past couple of months with interesting things happening in the broadband video world.&amp;nbsp; The &quot;video industry&quot; on the Internet is starting to emerge with great force and I&apos;m excited to be focused on this area.&amp;nbsp; I will try and be regular in posting and sharing thoughts again.</description>
			<guid>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/2004/04/20.html#a288</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2004 01:38:42 GMT</pubDate>
			<comments>http://radiocomments.userland.com/comments?u=113297&amp;amp;p=288&amp;amp;link=http%3A%2F%2Fradio.weblogs.com%2F0113297%2F2004%2F04%2F20.html%23a288</comments>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Onfolio, Micro-content, and Search Information Management</title>
			<link>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/2004/03/14.html#a287</link>
			<description>&lt;P&gt;Today, &lt;A href=&quot;http://www.onfolio.com&quot;&gt;Onfolio Inc. launched their namesake product Onfolio&lt;/A&gt;, helping to shape and define a new and important category in Internet software -- search information management.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Onfolio helps Internet users to easily collect, organize and share their research.&amp;nbsp; The product is built around the idea that &apos;search&apos; has become the most common Internet activity, yet end-users have had virtually no good tools to help them manage and share all the &quot;micro-content&quot; that they find on the Internet.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;The product tightly&amp;nbsp;integrates into Internet Explorer, Microsoft Office and the Windows desktop, enabling users to capture fragments of content from web pages, email, RSS feeds, and their desktop.&amp;nbsp; In essence, users create content &apos;collections&apos;, personal databases of micro-content that can be organized and searched locally, but then re-composed into reports that can be shared via email, posted as websites, and published as RSS feeds.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;http://www.forbes.com/technology/newswire/2004/03/14/rtr1298045.html&quot;&gt;Forbes.com characterizes it&apos;s essential role&lt;/A&gt;:&amp;nbsp; &quot;&lt;SPAN class=mainarttxt&gt;Onfolio faces head-on the problem of information overload, giving Internet users ways to capture and reuse the many tidbits they come across in everyday Internet use.&quot;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;The uses of the product touch anyone who seriously uses the Web, whether for personal or professional use.&amp;nbsp; The Onfolio website has some great &lt;A href=&quot;http://www.onfolio.com/product/scenarios.cfm&quot;&gt;usage examples&lt;/A&gt; to help spark your imagination.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Onfolio was founded by my brother J.J. Allaire, and also led by Allaire co-founders Adam Berrey and Charles Teague.&amp;nbsp; They&apos;ve done a great job creating an exceptionally useful product that will help all of us become more productive users of information on the Internet.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;I can personally attest that Onfolio has transformed my relationship with content on the Internet -- I am more in control of the surging amount of micro-content that floods websites, email, RSS feeds&amp;nbsp;and beyond.&amp;nbsp; Thanks guys!&lt;/P&gt;</description>
			<guid>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/2004/03/14.html#a287</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2004 02:39:53 GMT</pubDate>
			<comments>http://radiocomments.userland.com/comments?u=113297&amp;amp;p=287&amp;amp;link=http%3A%2F%2Fradio.weblogs.com%2F0113297%2F2004%2F03%2F14.html%23a287</comments>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Shaking up the Web Conferencing Market</title>
			<link>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/2004/02/20.html#a286</link>
			<description>&lt;P&gt;This week &lt;A href=&quot;http://www.convoq.com/&quot;&gt;Convoq launched their flagship&amp;nbsp;personal web conferencing&amp;nbsp;service&lt;/A&gt;, &lt;A href=&quot;http://www.convoq.com/Index.aspx?g=Products&amp;amp;i=ProductOverview#top&quot;&gt;As Soon As Present (ASAP)&lt;/A&gt;.&amp;nbsp; The launch is a milestone for the web conferencing marketplace which has to date been characterized by enterprise-focused price points, despite software experiences that have not yet graduated into the modern age of rich client interfaces and experiences and presence-enabled communications.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Convoq ASAP breaks a lot of ground in the convergence of presence management, rich media instant messaging and multi-participant web conferencing, and do this with an economics for the mass-market.&amp;nbsp; For less than $100 per year, users of ASAP can conduct an ulimited number of meetings with up to 25 participants.&amp;nbsp; Comparative pricing from Microsoft LiveMeeting (Placeware) and WebEx is in the tens of thousands of dollars.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;This approach to the market reflects Convoq&apos;s philosophy that real-time, rich media multi-participant online collaboration is ready to be an everyday productivity application, not a stovepipe system that is limited in its use to those &quot;premium&quot; sales calls or online demos.&amp;nbsp; The focus on making real-time collaboration more common is reflected in Convoq&apos;s thoughtful embrace of productivity-enhacing presence and convocation management features, helping either large or distributed organizations gather the right people at the right time in online settings.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;If you or your organization makes regular use of instant messaging and web conferencing in a professional (or personal!) context, I&apos;d encourage you to evaluate Convoq ASAP.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;As a board member of Convoq, it&apos;s very exciting to see this innovative communications service launch -- congrats to the entire Convoq team!&amp;nbsp; I can also say that while the 1.0 product accomplishes a lot, this team has an incredible vision and roadmap for where to take online communications and collaboration, so please stay tuned.&lt;/P&gt;</description>
			<guid>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/2004/02/20.html#a286</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2004 15:42:20 GMT</pubDate>
			<comments>http://radiocomments.userland.com/comments?u=113297&amp;amp;p=286&amp;amp;link=http%3A%2F%2Fradio.weblogs.com%2F0113297%2F2004%2F02%2F20.html%23a286</comments>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>When does Microsoft get commoditzed?</title>
			<link>http://www.corante.com/mooreslore/20040201.shtml#70047</link>
			<description>&lt;P&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;http://www.werblog.com&quot;&gt;Kevin Werbach&lt;/A&gt; pointed to &lt;A href=&quot;http://www.corante.com/mooreslore/20040201.shtml#70047&quot;&gt;this note about the fact that a baseline personal computer is now sub $500&lt;/A&gt;, following the trajectory of Moore&apos;s Law, yet the price of the software needed (from a professional perspective -- WinXP Pro and Office) costs more than the hardware.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;I&apos;ve been spending considerable time looking at the economics of software manufacturing and distribution&amp;nbsp;in the face of open source and offshore software development, and it strikes me that in the near future Microsoft will clearly face an erosion of their core software margin business as a result of the commoditizing economics of clone software manufactured in China at 1/100th (or less) the cost of manufacturing the software in Redmond.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/P&gt;</description>
			<guid>http://radio.weblogs.com/0113297/2004/02/17.html#a285</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2004 05:54:11 GMT</pubDate>
			<comments>http://radiocomments.userland.com/comments?u=113297&amp;amp;p=285&amp;amp;link=http%3A%2F%2Fradio.weblogs.com%2F0113297%2F2004%2F02%2F17.html%23a285</comments>
			</item>
		</channel>
	</rss>
