<?xml version='1.0'  encoding='iso-8859-1' ?>
 <!-- generator='bauRSSNews/1.0.0' -->
 <rss version='2.0' xmlns:content='http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/'>
<channel>
  <title><![CDATA[Digital Web Magazine - What's New]]></title>
  <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/]]></link>
  <description><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/]]></description>
  <language><![CDATA[]]></language>
  <copyright><![CDATA[]]></copyright>
  <lastBuildDate><![CDATA[Tue, 30 Nov 2004 12:47:00 PST]]></lastBuildDate>
  <pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 30 Nov 2004 12:47:00 PST]]></pubDate>
  <generator><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/]]></generator>
  <ttl><![CDATA[]]></ttl>
  <image>
    <title><![CDATA[Digital Web Magazine - What's New]]></title>
    <url><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/images/news/logo_digitalweb_rss.gif]]></url>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/]]></link>
    <width><![CDATA[]]></width>
    <height><![CDATA[]]></height>
  </image>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[New Issue of Digital Web Magazine]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/new_issue_of_digital_web_magazine_41/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Wed, 24 Nov 2004 21:48:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In this week's issue of Digital Web Magazine <a href="http://www.meryl.net/">Meryl K. Evans</a> returns with a great interview of WordPress creator <a href="http://www.digital-web.com/articles/matt_mullenweg/">Matt Mullenweg</a>.  Though, Matt is much more than just the creator of WordPress.  He is also one of the co-creators of XFN, the creator of Ping-O-Matic, photographer, and I hear he can also play some wicked jazz on the sax.  Also I am happy to announce that we have opened up our <a href="http://www.surveymonkey.com/s.asp?u=32023737321">annual readership survey</a>.  The annual readership survey helps the staff at Digital Web Magazine better understand the direction we need to be going for our content, the site, and the magazine as a whole.  Your input is extremely helpful in determining this, so please take a moment to complete the survey so we can provide a better site, better content and better services to fit your needs.  Lastly, this week's readership question is about giving back to the community.  Please take a second to <a href="http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/have_you_ever_contributed/">respond to the question</a>.  We are going to take a short break for the holidays so news may be slow until we return on Monday.  Thank you for reading.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Annual Readership Survey]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/annual_readership_survey/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Wed, 24 Nov 2004 20:30:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Well, it is that time of year again and we are going to start things a little early here at Digital Web Magazine.  Thanks to the help of Krista Stevens we have opened our <a href="http://www.surveymonkey.com/s.asp?u=32023737321">Annual Readership Survey</a> ahead of time in hopes to get your feedback before you start your holiday vacations.  So please, help us make Digital Web Magazine better by offering your input in this year's survey.  The survey will only take a short bit to complete.  Thank you for helping out and happy holidays.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Readership Question: Have you ever contributed?]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/have_you_ever_contributed/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Wed, 24 Nov 2004 19:40:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This week's readership question is a question related to the whole web community and not specifically just Digital Web Magazine.  Since its Thanksgiving here in the states I thought I would ask about giving back to the community.  With that said, this week's readership question is: <b>Have you ever contributed to your favorite community site? Why?</b>  Don't get me wrong, this is not a guilt trip for anyone who hasn't contributed articles or anything to this site.  I am just curious because there are many sites and projects out there like <a href="http://www.metafilter.com/donate_thanks.mefi">MetaFilter</a>, <a href="http://www.mozilla.org/foundation/donate.html">Mozilla</a>, <a href="http://www.eff.org/support/">EFF</a>, <a href="http://wordpress.org/donate/">WordPress</a>, and so forth that look for community contributions either of monetary form, articles, staff help, or otherwise.  So, through this question I hope to gain some insight into the logic of the community and why we do or do not contribute to our favorite sites.  Oh, and please, no need to brag about what you have done, a simple no or yes with an explanation of why will work fine.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Job openings at ZAAZ]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/job_openings_at_zaaz/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Wed, 24 Nov 2004 14:29:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I typically try not to make a habit out of posting job openings here on Digital Web Magazine but this kind of opportunity doesn't come along much at all.  My employer, <a href="http://www.zaaz.com/">ZAAZ</a>, is expanding and is currently looking for a <a href="http://www.zaaz.com/default.asp?pageID=jobs_department&amp;departmentID=1">Senior Designer</a>, as well as <a href="http://www.zaaz.com/default.asp?pageID=jobs_department&amp;departmentID=3">Project Manager</a>.  Both openings are for our Portland, Oregon office.  We are also looking for a <a href="http://www.zaaz.com/default.asp?pageID=jobs_department&amp;departmentID=1">Creative Director</a> for our Seattle office, where I work.  See the links mentioned above for more details.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ads and RSS]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/ads_and_rss/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Wed, 24 Nov 2004 12:53:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Nick Bradbury makes some excellent points about <a href="http://nick.typepad.com/blog/2004/11/rss_ads_what_no.html">RSS ad and what NOT to do</a>.  I highly recommend that you give his list a good read-through if you are considering adding ads to your RSS feeds.  As far as readers go, my take-away here is that if you don't like where this is going as far as RSS, simply unsubscribe.  The mass exile of subscribers to a feed will speak far more loudly than any amount of money an advertiser will throw at a site.  If there are no readers, what good are advertisements.  I am not saying this will stop them from including ads, but it will help define the status-quo within this market.  With that said, let me open the fire hose; what are your thoughts on ads in RSS feeds?  Add your two cents in the comments for this post.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[How to Quote]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/how_to_quote/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Wed, 24 Nov 2004 07:31:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Roger Johansson has an interesting post on 456 Berea Street about <a href="http://www.456bereastreet.com/archive/200411/quotations_and_citations_quoting_text/">Quotations and citations: quoting text</a>.  In the post he talks about the markup (with emphasis on the &quot;1&quot; element) and CSS needed to create a pull-quote.  A great read for anyone who is serious about their web content.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Generation Web Standards]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/generation_web_standards/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 23 Nov 2004 11:35:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Derek Featherstone makes some good comments about <a href="http://www.boxofchocolates.ca/archives/2004/11/22/growing-up-with-web-standards">Growing up With Web Standards</a>.  I may be a bit more pessimistic about the adoption tends for web standards because we said this very same thing 4 years ago.  That's not to say I think it won't happen... it will happen.  It's not a matter of if, it's a matter of when.  I hope that my children grow up with web standards as a commonplace... it would be reassuring to know they don't have to hack their CSS and XHTML.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[New Issue of Boxes and Arrows]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/new_issue_of_boxes_and_arrows_12/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 22 Nov 2004 21:28:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A new issue of Boxes and Arrows is out.  In this issue you will find a great article by Andy Schriever entitled <a href="http://www.boxesandarrows.com/archives/the_knowledgemodel_driven_enterprise.php">The Knowledge-Model Driven Enterprise</a>, but the most interesting thing for me was Christina Wodtke's piece on <a href="http://www.boxesandarrows.com/archives/redesigning_boxes_and_arrows.php">Redesigning Boxes and Arrows</a> where she mentions <a href="http://www.boxesandarrows.com/archives/redesigning_boxes_and_arrows.php?page=2">the winners</a> of the redesign contest.  You can see <a href="http://www.boxesandarrows.com/contest/anon-album/">all of the entries</a> here.  It's interesting to see how many of them look like Digital Web Magazine from a structural standpoint (and there is <a href="http://www.digital-web.com/about/staff/christina_wodtke/">good reason</a> why the IA is similar), I think we will be seeing more content-rich sites break way from the blog model and move into the magazine model in the near future.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[JJG is Alive]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/jjg_is_alive/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 22 Nov 2004 12:57:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[It looks like <a href="http://blog.jjg.net/">Jesse James Garrett</a> has resurrected his blog.  You can expect to find great information on IA, UX and other things that cross JJG's path.  Welcome back my friend!  Also see the Digital Web Magazine <a href="http://www.digital-web.com/articles/jeffrey_veen_and_jesse_james_garrett/">interview</a> we did with JJG back in 2002.  [from <a href="http://www.dashes.com/anil/2004/11/22/jjg_is_back">Anil Dash</a>]]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Typography 101]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/typography_101/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 22 Nov 2004 12:48:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Ellen Lupton has created an online companion site <a href="http://www.papress.com/thinkingwithtype/">Thinking with Type</a> for <a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1568984480/digitalwebmagazi"><cite>Thinking with Type: A Critical Guide for Designers, Writers, Editors, & Students</cite></a>.  It's a great resource for typography information.  The site reminds me a lot of <a href="http://counterspace.motivo.com/">CounterSpace</a> with it's attention to detail.  [from <a href="http://www.456bereastreet.com/archive/200411/thinking_with_type/">456 Berea Street</a>]]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Facets of Navigation]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/facets_of_navigation/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 30 Nov 2004 12:47:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Peter Van Dijck posts about <a href="http://poorbuthappy.com/ease/archives/2004/11/30/2292/iaslash-a-z-indexes-for-web-sites-usage-and-implementation">A-Z Indexes</a> and contrasts it to search and controlled vocabularies.  Digital Web Magazine has a <a href="http://www.digital-web.com/titles/">A-Z Index</a> as well.  The qualitative data we are seeing from the current <a href="http://www.surveymonkey.com/s.asp?u=32023737321">Annual Readership Survey</a> thus far show that the A-Z Index is the third most used facet on the site with the topic map being first and, of course, the internal search engine being second.  Quantitative data analysis shows that while the topic map is the most used facet, the category index is the second most used and the A-Z index is the third most used facet.  I am curious to hear what your take on this is.  If available, what facets do you see <em>your</em> site's users using the most?  Is it the A-Z Index, topic map, categorical index, chronological index, author index, or internal search engine? Or do you provide any of these facets on your site at all?  And if not, why?  I'll be speaking more about how to use both of these methods to help inform design coming up in March for <a href="http://www.sxsw.com/interactive/">SXSWi</a>.  I'll post more information about that presentation later.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nick Finck on iStockPhoto]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/nick_finck_on_istockphoto/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 29 Nov 2004 20:35:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.istockphoto.com/">iStockPhoto</a> has published an interview of <a href="http://www.istockphoto.com/article_view.php?ID=25">someone you may know</a>.  I had a lot of fun doing this interview and photo shoot.  Topics covered are balancing form and function, web awards, Digital Web Magazine <a href="http://www.kclinephotography.com/">Kelly Cline</a> took the creative photos, Brianna Wettlaufer asked the questions, and Bruce Livingstone helped manage things.  I hope you enjoy reading it as much as I did responding to the interview.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Keep Personas Simple]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/keep_personas_simple/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 29 Nov 2004 08:26:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Don Norman has posted the sidebar content that is to be published in <cite>The Persona Lifecycle: Keeping people in mind during product design</cite>.  The post is entitled <a href="http://www.jnd.org/dn.mss/adhoc_personas_em.html">Ad-Hoc Personas &amp; Empathetic Focus</a>.  I think the takeaway here is that, as Henrik Olsen said, &quot;Personas doesn't have to be rocket science.&quot;  Often times I find web teams a usability experts stressing over getting the factual data nailed down and checking to ensure that every persona possible is accounted for.  This is overkill and don't really cater to the purpose personas at large.  Keep it simple, go with what you know, let the rest fall in place.  [from <a href="http://www.guuui.com/posting.php?id=1601">GUUUI</a>]]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[UXnet]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://www.digital-web.com/news/2004/11/uxnet/]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[news-rss@digital-web.com (Nick Finck)]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 28 Nov 2004 23:22:00 PST]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[While we were busy eating some turkey over the holiday weekend it appears that UXnet was busy publishing an <a href="http://uxnet.org/blog/2004/11/uxnet-update.html">update</a> on the status of the network.  As both a Local Ambassador and Individual Supporter nothing makes me happier than to see a group like this really take off like we have in the last six months.  But this is by no means where the story ends and this doesn't happen without some serious effort.  UXnet needs the help of the community to move forward.  I encourage you to sign up for one of the <a href="http://uxnet.org/initiatives/">initiatives</a> or to simply get involved on a local level.  With that said, if you are in the local Pacific Northwest, please <a href="http://nickfinck.com/contact.html">contact me</a> or the <a href="http://uxnet.org/contact/councilmail.html">UXnet Council</a> directly to see how you can play a role in moving forward.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
