<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>WinXPnews</title>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com</link>
<description>WinXPnews™ is the world's first and largest weekly B2C-zine uniquely focused on the many millions of new Microsoft Windows XP users.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 1996-2004 Sunbelt Software All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
<managingEditor>feedback@winxpnews.com (Deb Shinder)</managingEditor>
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2004 18:24:48 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<ttl>1440</ttl>
<item><title>Will Humans Catch Computer Viruses?</title>
<description>As if it weren't enough to have to worry about our computers getting infected with viruses, what will happen when the science of cybernetics joins man and machine? Will the bad guys be trying to hack our brains? This week's editorial explores a future where those who aren't cyborgs are out of step. In the followup, our readers sound off about social engineering.
</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=152</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>Social Engineers: They're Out to Get Your Information</title>
<description>You might have heard about "social engineers" but do you know what they are and why you should be on the lookout for them? Find out in this week's editor's corner. In the followup, more on spyware and CounterSpy.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=151</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>Is it Just Spam or is it Something Worse?</title>
<description>What's worse than spam? Spyware! We announce the release of a new tool that can help you detect, delete and protect yourself against all this malware. Also this week, learn how to identify and protect yourself from the newest phishing attacks designed to get your to divulge your personal information.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=150</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>Big Brother Listening In On Chat Rooms?</title>
<description>Everyone knows by now that e-mail is not necessarily private. What about your online chat conversations? Did you know the U.S. government recently funded a study on monitoring chat rooms? Is this another step toward Big Brother, or a necessary tactic against terrorists? In our followup, our readers sound off about wireless security and whether or not is should be mandatory.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=149</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>Will the FBI Come After You If...?</title>
<description>Wireless networking is convenient and cool - but there are known security issues. Now there's something new to worry about: will you find the FBI on your doorstep if you fail to properly secure your wireless network? In the followup segment, readers respond to last week's editorial on spyware, telling us the problem is getting worse.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=148</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>Spyware, The Next Chapter</title>
<description>Spyware has become a huge problem, and is now worse than viruses. How has your experience with spyware been since we last discussed it? In the followup, our readers tell us whether they believe P2P file sharing should be banned, and why or why not.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=147</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>Should P2P Be Banned? </title>
<description>Some people want to shut down P2P file sharing technology completely, because it can be used for violating copyright law. Is this blaming the technology? Read our editorial in this week's WinXPNews. In the followup, readers sound off on technology that prevents printers and copiers from copying money.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=146</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>Copying Money?</title>
<description>Did you realize that your printer or copier might be smart enough to detect what you're copying and tell you "no?" Just try to copy a twenty dollar bill on some of the new equipment. This week, we take a look at a new anti-counterfeiting technology and its implications for computer users. In the followup, you tell us how you feel about hiring hackers as network security advisors.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=145</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>Hiring Hackers: Smart Tactic or Bad Move?</title>
<description>Do you get a little bit annoyed when you read about some hacker being caught breaking into government computers and then, instead of being jailed, he ends up with a high paying "security consultant" job? Looks like that trend is finally dying out. And in our Followup, readers tell us what they think about criminalizing peer to peer file sharing.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=144</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>Share Your Files and Go Directly to Jail?</title>
<description>You knew you could get sued for engaging in file sharing over Peer to Peer networks. Soon it may become even more dangerous. New legislation before Congress would put file sharers in jail. In our followup, readers sound off about the "black boxes" (Event Data Recorders) that come with some of today's new cars.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=143</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>Is the "Black Box" Spying on You?</title>
<description>Everybody knows about the "black boxes" on airplanes, but did you know your car might be recording what you do? Read about it in this week's editorial. And we say a big "thank you" to all the Gmail users who donated their invitations so other WinXPNews readers could get accounts.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=142</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>More Service Pack 2 News and Blues</title>
<description>Readers' e-mail about XP Service Pack 2 keeps rolling in. This week, we report on more SP2 experiences and incompatibilities. In the followup section, you tell us what you think about Microsoft's new "dumbed down" version of Windows XP.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=141</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>Do You Want a Dumbed-Down Version of XP?</title>
<description>Some folks are up in arms over Microsoft's new Windows XP Starter Edition, a low-cost, cut-rate version of Windows to be marketed in selected countries. Read about the controversy and let us know what you think. In the followup section, the mail is still coming in about SP2, and we'll keep reporting the good, the bad and the ugly.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=140</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>The Spy(ware) That Snagged Me</title>
<description>Has your computer been invaded against your will? Is your software "phoning home" to report on your Web surfing habits and other activities? There are hundreds of spyware programs out there, eager to get their hooks into your computer. Read "The Spy(ware) That Snagged Me" for more about this growing problem. And find out about the latest reported problems with Service Pack 2 in our followup.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=139</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item><item><title>Service Pack 2: It's Out There</title>
<description>We've all been waiting for it, and now everybody's talking about it. Some say it's the greatest thing since apple pie. Others say it will destroy your computer? Who should you believe? Do you dare try it for yourself? XP Service Pack 2 - it's out there. In the Followup segment, our readers (99% of them, anyway) love getting Googled.</description>
<link>http://www.winxpnews.com/rd/rsd.cfm?id=138</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item></channel>
</rss>
