<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<!--  RSS generated by DevX on Wed, 01 Dec 2004 01:09:02 PST -->
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>DevX: Open Source Articles</title>
<link>http://www.devx.com</link>
<description>Latest DevX Content</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2002 DevX</copyright>
<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss</docs>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2004 01:09:02 PST</lastBuildDate>
<image>
<title>DevX</title>
<url>http://services.devx.com/outgoing/devxwire.gif</url>
<link>http://www.DevX.com</link>
</image>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[No-cost System Lockdown, Part 2: Open Source IDS in Use]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[<a href="/security/Article/22442" target="new">Part 1</a> gave you a rundown of the most popular open source IDS solutions. Now learn how to protect your servers by employing common, practical uses for these solutions.]]></description>
<link>http://www.devx.com/security/Article/22476?trk=DXRSS_OPNSRC</link>
<author>white@extrasy.net (Alexander Prohorenko)</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2004 16:05:34 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Open Source Intrusion Detection: No-cost System Lockdown]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[Have you found commercial intrusion detection systems (IDS) to be overkill or just too expensive? Open source IDS projects offer a use-only-what-you-need alternative&mdash;and of course, they're free. Get a rundown of the most popular non-commercial IDS solutions.]]></description>
<link>http://www.devx.com/security/Article/22442?trk=DXRSS_OPNSRC</link>
<author>white@extrasy.net (Alexander Prohorenko)</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2004 17:57:53 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[SOAP's Alive: Try the New Native SOAP Extensions for PHP]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[With PHP5, Web services and everybody's favorite open source Web development language are now native pals. ]]></description>
<link>http://www.devx.com/webdev/Article/22338?trk=DXRSS_OPNSRC</link>
<author>lmoroney@philotic.com (Laurence Moroney)</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2004 17:45:25 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Use SWT Listener Classes Effectively for Responsive Java UIs]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[By using the SWT listener classes effectively as this article prescribes, you can win the hearts of your Java application users with highly responsive GUIs.]]></description>
<link>http://www.devx.com/Java/Article/22264?trk=DXRSS_OPNSRC</link>
<author>dsraghu@hotmail.com (Raghu Donepudi)</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2004 18:41:12 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Build an Object-oriented File System in PHP]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[Using a simple file storage convention and some PHP code, you can create a hierarchical file system that mimics many object-oriented concepts, facilitates reuse, and simplifies your Web development efforts.]]></description>
<link>http://www.devx.com/webdev/Article/22240?trk=DXRSS_OPNSRC</link>
<author>devx@toykeeper.net (Scott Scriven)</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2004 11:40:53 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Validating Email Addresses with Regular Expressions in PHP]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[This class uses regular expressions and PHP to validate email addresses for misprints or false entries.  ]]></description>
<link>http://www.devx.com/tips/Tip/22209?trk=DXRSS_OPNSRC</link>
<author>Cem Aykan aykan@coe.neu.edu</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2004 19:39:40 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[How to Install and Use Cloudscape]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[IBM's open-source embedded database delivers a full relational DBMS with remarkably low administrative overhead. This no-hassle design applies to developing for Cloudscape as well.]]></description>
<link>http://www.devx.com/IBMCloudscape/Article/22197?trk=DXRSS_OPNSRC</link>
<author>abinstock@pacificdataworks.com (Andrew Binstock)</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2004 02:14:12 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[WindowBuilder Pro: Advanced Java GUI Creation in Eclipse]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[Want to build Java user interfaces without drowning in the minutia of the Java GUI libraries? WindowBuilder Pro may be the tool for you. Learn all about this Eclipse plug-in as Jason Morris puts it to the test.]]></description>
<link>http://www.devx.com/Java/Article/22186?trk=DXRSS_OPNSRC</link>
<author>counsulting@morristechnicalsolutions.com (Jason Morris)</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2004 21:28:01 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Get AMPed over Uniform Server and Build a Data-driven Web Site in Nothing Flat]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[Web development gets easier all the time, but Uniform Server, an open source project that packs up the ease and power of the 'AMP' platform, takes simplicity to the edge of embarrassing. Go from zero to Web hero in minutes by using our sample blog project to teach yourself the ease and power of AMP. ]]></description>
<link>http://www.devx.com/webdev/Article/22169?trk=DXRSS_OPNSRC</link>
<author>lmoroney@philotic.com (Laurence Moroney)</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2004 20:42:11 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Find Programs or Libraries Related to a Particular Keyword on a UNIX Platform]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[Learn how to use the <i>apropos</i> utility to find out what programs installed on your machine will handle content of a given type. ]]></description>
<link>http://www.devx.com/tips/Tip/22159?trk=DXRSS_OPNSRC</link>
<author>Karthik Kumar kaykaydreamz@yahoo.com</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2004 14:33:29 PST</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>

