<?xml version='1.0'  encoding='iso-8859-1' ?>
 <!-- generator='bauRSSNews/1.0.0' -->
 <rss version='2.0' xmlns:content='http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/'>
<channel>
  <title><![CDATA[Creative Commons Blog - rss]]></title>
  <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org]]></link>
  <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
  <language><![CDATA[]]></language>
  <copyright><![CDATA[]]></copyright>
  <lastBuildDate><![CDATA[]]></lastBuildDate>
  <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
  <generator><![CDATA[]]></generator>
  <ttl><![CDATA[]]></ttl>
  <image>
    <title><![CDATA[Creative Commons: weblog]]></title>
    <url><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/images/logo_trademark.gif]]></url>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog]]></link>
    <width><![CDATA[]]></width>
    <height><![CDATA[]]></height>
  </image>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[INQUIRER does Magnatune]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5081]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Snarky tech news site the INQUIRER <a href="http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=19868">interviews Magnatune's John Buckman</a>, who is refreshingly direct.</p>

<blockquote>Buckman: We sell a little over 1000 albums a month - about $10,000 a month - and this has been stable for about 6 months. Music Licensing has grown from about $2,000 a month 6 months ago to about $10,000 a month now. I expect most future growth to come through sales through other channels, as well as music licensing.</blockquote>

<p>For more check out <a href="http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=19868">the interview</a> and <a href="http://blogs.magnatune.com/">John's blog</a>, including his recent <a href="http://blogs.magnatune.com/buckman/2004/11/the_online_musi.html">take on the online music space</a>.

<p>All Magnatune releases (from <a href="http://www.magnatune.com/info/stats/">174</a> artists!) are under a Creative Commons <a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/1.0/">Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike</a> license.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.magnatune.com/genres/">Tune in.</a></p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Big Sonic Sharing]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5080]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p align="center"><a href="http://bigsonic.com"><img src="http://bigsonic.com/logos/bsr_logo.gif" border="0"/></a></p>

<p>Pittsburgh based label <a href="http://bigsonic.com">Big Sonic Recordings</a> has released its catalog under a Creative Commons <a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/2.0/">Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs</a> license.</p>

<blockquote>At Big Sonic Recordings, you'll notice that all of our artists give away all of their music for free, and every artist has an online store full of merchandise that you can purchase if you wish to support them. It is the Big Sonic pledge to keep the music free, and find alternative ways for artists to be compensated for their work in this new digital age.</blockquote>

<p>Big Sonic claims to be "home of the sick and twisted" but I'd say they're alright.  The kids might enjoy the <a href="http://bigsonic.com/lc_music.php">brand spanking new album</a> from <a href="http://bigsonic.com/lc_music.php">Liquid Crutch</a>.</p>

<blockquote>
<p>Q: Aren’t you guys hurting yourselves in the long run?
<br/>
A: With what? We have a disclaimer stating that if you want to use our music for, say, a soundtrack, just contact us for permission. We make music to make music and go completely ape shit on stage. If it were money we wanted, we would have gotten different jobs.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><a href="http://bigsonic.com/lc_interview.php">Rock on!</a></p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Flash/AfterEffects/Video Design Person Wanted]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5077]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>We'd like to produce a short, <a href="http://creativecommons.org/learnmore">new animated/motion graphics film</a>, and we need a great designer and/or animator to help us do so on a fairly tight deadline. You should know how to animate in Flash or After Effects (or both) and have experience with any necessary drawing tools, like Adobe Illustrator. You should have the confidence and skill to help us produce a film of at least the caliber of <a href="http://creativecommons.org/learnmore">our previous pieces</a>. No need to be a writer (we'll collaborate on the script) or an audio engineer (though if you are one or know one, that's great). Location in the Bay Area and enthusiasm for the work of Creative Commons are big bonuses. Send an email ASAP to press@creativecommons.org if you are interested. Please include (1) a CV, (2) a list of the animated or graphic design pieces you've done, (3) a link to any such pieces that are now online, and (4) all your contact information. Thanks!</p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Opsound Party: CBGB NYC December 2]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5076]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>If you're in New York City get over to <a href="http://www.cbgb.com/">CBGB Lounge</a> next Thursday for a <a href="http://www.opsound.org/opsound/events/catalpaparty.html">party celebrating Opsound's first CD release</a>.</p>

<p align="center"><a href="http://www.opsound.org/opsound/events/catalpaparty.html"><img src="http://www.opsound.org/opsound/events/eventpics/catalpaparty1.gif" border="0"/></a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.opsound.org/opsound/opshop.html">Buy</a> the CD and <a href="http://www.opsound.org/opsound/pool/catalpa.html">download the MP3s</a> by the band <a href="http://catalpacatalpa.com/">Catalpa Catalpa</a>.  All tracks are CC licensed, as is everything in the <a href="http://www.opsound.org/opsound/pool.html">Opsound Pool</a>.</p>

<p>Congratulations to Opsound founder <a href="http://www.highlala.com/front.html">Sal Randolph</a> and all of the Opsound artists!</a></p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Perdition Remix Contest]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5075]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Positron! Records, whose recent <a href="http://www.positronrecords.com/cc/">adoption</a> of Creative Commons licenses was <a href="http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5067">noted</a> on this weblog two days ago, is encouraging users to take advantage of their first licensed album with a <a href="http://www.positronrecords.com/artists/micro/contest/index.html">remix contest</a>. They've helpfully made a <a href="http://www.positronrecords.com/artists/micro/contest/perdition_rmx_kit.zip">remix kit</a> containing vocal tracks and loops from the target track, <a href="http://www.positronrecords.com/artists/micro/contest/perdition.mp3">Perdition</a>.</p>

<p>[<a href="http://homepage.mac.com/robmyers/weblog/C1592552572/E1845105247/index.html"><em>via Rob Myers</em></a>]</p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[ccPublisher Updated: Now With More Crunchy Metadata!]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5074]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Just in time for Thanksgiving (and yet another thing to be thankful for), we've released an update to ccPublisher.  ccPublisher 0.9.9 (<a href="http://mirrors.creativecommons.org/software/publisher/ccpublisher-0.9.9.msi">windows</a>, <a href="http://mirrors.creativecommons.org/software/publisher/ccpublisher-0.9.9.dmg">mac</a>) adds support for Internet Archive keywords and description information.  Supplying this information will allow visitors to the Archive find your work, become your fan, and stalk you by going through your trash.  Well, probably (hopefully?) not the last one,  but you get the picture: better exposure through metadata.</p>

<p>Not familiar with ccPublisher?  Check out our <a href="http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/4507">initial release</a> announcement.</p>

<p>This is hopefully our final beta release before 1.0, so download it and give it a try.  You can <a href="mailto:nathan@creativecommons.org">email me</a> bugs, or (even better) submit them <a href="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/?group_id=80503&atid=559966">at SourceForge</a>.  Enjoy!</p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Thanksgiving]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5073]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Tomorrow the U.S. celebrates Thanksgiving. It's my favorite holiday. Just as the days are getting dark too soon, the wind (even here in Northern California) getting a precocious frost to it, and the mad dash towards yet another <em>big milestone</em> New Year taking stride with only an imaginary starter's whistle blown, we're obliged to pause. To reunite with friends and loved ones. To think about why we've done so. To say thanks for everyone and everything we've got, however much we might or might not deserve it. Yes, it sounds corny and quaint. But that's me.</p>

<p>Most times, with most people I know, we say our thanks to God, or to life. I'm all for both but tend to prefer to do so privately. What I've always wanted to do very publicly -- but have never done, as far as I remember -- is to say thanks to people. Doubtless it's not an original idea, but we at this organization, if you've noticed, really like unoriginality.</p> 

<p>So, thanks to people. Thanks, Creative Commons, for my job.</p> 

<p>A job's not a person, but it is people. For me the most important thing about Creative Commons, even beyond the concept and the service (which I sort of dig, too), is the people. That's the staff, the board, our advisors, volunteers, sponsors, supporters -- all of whom I'll talk about some later -- but it's really more about the wildly great number of you using the tools or re-using their fruits in ways we never anticipated.</p> 

<p>I was first drawn to study copyright and cyberlaw, I remember pretty clearly, because most cases were ultimately stories about weird and interesting people. Plaintiff or Defendant or often both, they were people who wanted to become bigger people by extending their voices. In school or now, that's subject matter -- that's a vocation -- to be thankful for.</p> 

<p>As a bonus, the people studying and arguing copyright law were, and remain, the weirdest and most interesting lawyers.</p>

<p>So, take the union of those two groups of weird and interesting people, add the Internet and some civics lessons from pioneers of coding, and you've got a nice candidate for your gratitude.</p> 

<p>Stay tuned for more givings of thanks (if you can stomach any more earnestness) in a series of blog posts about a specific few of the people above.</p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[SF MOMA and the University of Maine]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5069]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>I had the pleasure of speaking on two panels recently.  Last Thursday, I participated in <a href="http://sfmoma.org/calendar/calendar_event.asp?eventid=716&etype=2&func=repeat">The Open Source Paradigm</a> at the <a href="http://www.sfmoma.org">SF MOMA</a>, an event aimed to explore the history of open-source, and find new applications of its concepts in art.  A few interesting ideas came out of the panel including a <i>No Military Use</i> license, and how it benefits everyone to open-source your french fries (in this case, sharing is good because it keeps you skinny and wins favor with your friends). Attribution to <a href="http://art.berkeley.edu/niemeyer/">Greg Niemeyer</a> for the fries, and a gentleman from the audience for the <i>No Military Use</i> license. The event was presented by SMAC, the San Francisco Media Arts Council.
</p>

<p>
On Saturday I was at <a href="http://library.umaine.edu/coic/overview.htm">The Conference of the Intellectual Commons</a> at <a href="http://www.umaine.edu/">The University of Maine</a>.  It was amazing to hear several speakers mention Creative Commons throughout the day, including <a href="http://creativecommons.org/about/people#1">Hal Abelson, Board member of Creative Commons</a>, who gave a great talk on <a href="http://ocw.mit.edu/index.html">MIT's OpenCourseWare</a> and <a href="https://dspace.mit.edu/index.jsp">DSpace</a>.  This conference was intended, at least partially, to initiate a conversation as to how the Univesity of Maine could become a leader in open-access publishing, and in a "some rights reserved" approach in general. 
</p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Rediscover Culture with Firefox & CC Search]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5068]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.spreadfirefox.com/?q=affiliates&amp;id=0&amp;t=80"><img border="0" alt="Get Firefox!" title="Get Firefox!" align="right" src="http://www.spreadfirefox.com/community/images/affiliates/Buttons/120x60/rediscover.gif"/></a></a>

Cool thing about <a href="http://getfirefox.com/">Firefox 1.0</a> number 75387: access to the <a href="http://search.creativecommons.org">Creative Commons search engine</a> is <a href="http://creativecommons.org/press-releases/entry/5064">built in</a>.  If you're already using Firefox 1.0, just click on the search drop-down to the upper right of the browser window and select Creative Commons.  If you're not using Firefox, <a href="http://getfirefox.com">get with the program!</a></p>

<p>The Creative Commons search engine crawls the web for content marked with Creative Commons license metadata and utilizes the same to help you find content to use and build upon, under terms you're willing to accept -- <a href="http://creativecommons.org/technology/metadata/what">Semantic Web</a>, anyone?  We've had a <a href="http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/4028">prototype</a> up since March and <a href="http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/4388">soft launched</a> the current <a href="http://nutch.org">Nutch</a>-based engine in September.  Firefox integration is a major step forward.
</p>

<p align="center"><img src="http://mirrors.creativecommons.org/blimg/firefox-cc-070.png"/>
<br/><em>Searching for "free culture" via Firefox 1.0 and the Creative Commons search engine.</em></p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Another non-evil label: Positron!]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5067]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.positronrecords.com/cc/">Positron! Records</a> follows the lead of <strong>the</strong> non-evil record label, <a href="http://magnatune.com">Magnatune</a>:</p>

<p><a href="http://www.positronrecords.com/cc/"><img src="http://mirrors.creativecommons.org/blimg/positron_records_logo.gif" /></a></p>

<blockquote><p>Positron! Records is pleased to announce that our artists now have the option of releasing their works under Creative Commons licenses.</p>

<p>
Unlike those who suffer from what we like to call "major label retardation," we here at Positron! have <em>never</em> believed it was bad thing for our supporters to share our music with their friends. The Creative Commons licenses we use legally allow you to share songs from these records on peer-to-peer networks. In addition, you can sample portions of these songs for use in your own compositions, whether they are mash-ups for your friends, or a commercial release. It is our way of both thumbing our nose at the ridiculous state of copyright law in this country, and letting you, our customer and supporter, know that you are not a criminal, but a trusted ally in the war against corporate stupidity.</p>
</blockquote>

[<a href="http://gonze.com/weblog/story/11-22-4"><em>via Lucas Gonze</em></a>]]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Creative Commons France licenses now available]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5066]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>This Friday at the National Assembly in Paris, Creative Commons released the <a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/2.0/fr/legalcode">French versions</a> of our licenses.</p>

<p>Hats off to project lead Melanie Dulong de Rosnay and the rest of <a href="http://creativecommons.org/worldwide/fr/">the Creative Commons France team</a>.</p> 

<p>France joins Austria, Brazil, Canada, Finland, Germany, Japan, the Netherlands, Spain, and Taiwan in offering <a href="http://creativecommons.org/worldwide/">localized Creative Commons licenses</a>.</p>

<p>Read the <a href="http://creativecommons.org/press-releases/entry/5063">press release</a>.</p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Engadget on mashups, call for tutorials]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5062]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.engadget.com/">Engadget</a> is a great all-around blog about technology and the latest gadgets, but in the past few weeks they've began doing a "podcast" which is sort of like a home-brewed radio show, saved as mp3s and shared on their site. <a href="http://www.engadget.com/entry/1234000097020901/">This week's podcast</a> has an interesting segment on "Mashing the Planet," their call to arms (<a href="http://www.flashenabled.com/mashtheplanet.txt">here in text</a>) to teach people how to use audio tools to make mashups (including legal ones with the WIRED CD) and especially to create good tutorials so anyone can pick up an audio program and make something good.<br />
<br />
I chopped <a href="http://mirrors.creativecommons.org/blimg/engadget-on-mashups.mp3">the segment out of the show here</a>, and it's about 5 minutes long. They discuss the state of audio tools, the lack of tutorials, Creative Commons, and the music industry's reaction to mashups.<br />
<br />
A few months ago, we brainstormed ways to improve the Creative Commons site and part of it was writing lots of tutorials for how to use applications like Photoshop, ACID, and iMovie to make images, audio, and video using existing freely downloadable Creative Commons licensed works. We quickly found out it's a big endeavor and hope the Mash the Planet idea blossoms into a full-on tutorial website we can someday point users to.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[The WIRED CD: MP3.com]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5060]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>There is a <a href="http://www.mp3.com/MP3+Insider%3A+Free+MP3s+from+the+Creative+Commons/stories/1074.html">nice piece up at MP3.com</a> by Eliot Van Buskirk about (what else?) the <a href="http://creativecommons.org/wired">WIRED CD</a>.</p>

<p>Watch this blog for some juicy news regarding the CD very soon.</p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[One artist's view of filesharing]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5059]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.scottandrew.com/">Scott Andrew Lepera</a>, previously <a href="http://creativecommons.org/audio/musicians">featured</a> in our Audio section a couple years back, has <a href="http://www.scottandrew.com/main/entries/001148">a great post today looking at the benefits and costs of filesharing</a> to a small, independent artist. He weighs the pros and cons of both filesharing and digital rights management (DRM), and comes to a different conclusion than he once held. It's interesting stuff that a lot of other net-based musicians can likely relate to.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Launch in France]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5058]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Tomorrow, on Friday 19 November, the French launch of the Creative
Commons licenses will be celebrated in Paris. There will be a press
conference cum roundtable discussion in the French National Assembly
starting at 2pm (Assemblée Nationale, 126 rue de l'Université, 75007
Paris, salle 62-17) and a launch party at the Maison des Métallos, 94
rue Jean-Pierre Timbaud, 75011 Paris, at 8pm. You are welcome to attend
and get in touch with CC staff.]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[W3C10]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5089]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Our World Wide Web Consortium representative <a href="http://creativecommons.org/about/people#13">Ben Adida</a> will be present at meetings concurrent with the consortium's <a href="http://w3.org/2004/09/W3C10.html">tenth anniversary celebration</a>.</p>

<p>Ben has been doing important work to standardize <a href="http://lists.w3.org/Archives/Public/public-rdf-in-xhtml-tf/">embedding RDF metadata in HTML</a> (I find the <a href="http://www.formsplayer.com/notes/rdf-a.html">RDF/A</a> proposal particularly compelling).</p>

<p>Services like the <a href="http://search.creativecommons.org">Creative Commons search engine</a> build on RDF metadata describing licensed works that you get automatically when you <a href="http://creativecommons.org/license/">choose a license</a>.  The W3C's RDF-in-HTML standardization efforts promise to increase the value of CC metadata, opening paths to integration with many new applications.</p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[La creation en partage]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5088]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>CC French project lead Melanie Dulong de Rosnay and Daniele Bourcier
have just published '<a href="http://fr.creativecommons.org/iCommonsAtTheDigitalAge.pdf">International Commons at the Digital Age - la creation en partage</a>', a book with
some valuable chapters on our first experiences with the internationalized CC licenses.</p>

<p>The book was written as a contribution to a day-long event in Paris on
November 19th to celebrate the launch of the French CC licenses.</p>

<p>For this occasion (photographs and some abstracts to follow in these
pages) Melanie had organized several panels at the French National
Assembly debating the merits of the CC approach from a variety of
different perspectives (academia, the publishing industry, politics,
science, the arts). The celebration continued into the wee hours at the
Maison de Metallo in downtown Paris with live music acts, poetry
readings, website presentations and fair trade drinks.</p>

<p>Many thanks to Melanie for all her enthusiasm and her splendid
organization of this event.</p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[The WIRED CD: La Vanguardia]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5085]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>La Vanguardia, the most popular newspaper in Catalonia, ran <a href="http://www.lavanguardia.es/public/series/20041128/51170424942.html">a story</a> on the <a href="http://creativecommons.org/wired">WIRED CD</a> this weekend.</p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[We Don't Need No Exploitation]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[http://creativecommons.org/weblog/entry/5083]]></link>
    <comments><![CDATA[]]></comments>
    <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
    <pubDate><![CDATA[]]></pubDate>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
    <guid isPermaLink='false'><![CDATA[]]></guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><blockquote>A group of former pupils at a London comprehensive school are poised to win thousands of pounds in unpaid royalties for singing on Pink Floyd's classic Another Brick In The Wall 25 years ago.</blockquote></p>

<p>This is a <a href="http://www.thisislondon.com/news/articles/14980155?source=Evening%20Standard">great story</a>.</p>

<p>I'm looking forward to the guy who screams "<a href="http://www.songmeanings.net/lyric.php?lid=19">How can yew have any pudding if you haven't eaten yer meat?</a>" bringing the next lawsuit. (If for no other reason, I bet he's a really interesting-looking bloke 25 years later.)</p>]]></description>
    <status>New</status>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
