<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Sunbelt Software New Products</title><link>http://www.sunbelt-software.com/recent.cfm</link><description>Sunbelt Software is the World's #1 Windows NT-2000-XP Tools Provider. Here are our most recently added products.</description><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright 1996-2004 Sunbelt Software All Rights Reserved.</copyright><managingEditor>webmaster@sunbelt-software.com</managingEditor><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2004 17:48:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>10</ttl><item><title>New Product: Sunbelt Security Pack</title><description>Sunbelt Security Pack. </description><link>http://www.sunbelt-software.com/product.cfm?id=150</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Product: CounterSpy Enterprise - Preview</title><description>CounterSpy Enterprise - Preview. CounterSpy Enterprise is first in true enterprise-ready anti- spyware. It is a powerful policy-based second generation product that detects and deletes over 30 categoeries of malware. The spyware threat database is updated both by Sunbelt's own Spyware Research Team and the thousands of people in Sunbelt's Spyware Fighters Network (SFN).</description><link>http://www.sunbelt-software.com/product.cfm?id=400</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Product: CounterSpy</title><description>CounterSpy. CounterSpy is a powerful anti-spyware tool that detects, deletes and protects your personal computer from a broad range of malicious software. There's a big difference between the freeware out there and CounterSpy™. Of course CounterSpy searches and destroys existing spyware on your computer, but it also has sophisticated protection against recurring spyware threats, reducing the chances of getting new spyware. Think of it as a "spy-wall". Arm your computer with our free 15-day trial and re-experience the Internet with a newfound peace of mind.</description><link>http://www.sunbelt-software.com/product.cfm?id=410</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Product: Fortress-NT/2000</title><description>Fortress-NT/2000. Protects your system's security and resources</description><link>http://www.sunbelt-software.com/product.cfm?id=677</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Product: ServerVision</title><description>ServerVision. Prevent downtime and intrusions. ServerVision™ gives you the power to see the health and status of your distributed servers in a single glance. Its best feature is that it is easy to set up, easy to run, and easy to afford. System Admins love it. Download the 30-day eval and see for yourself how easy it really is.</description><link>http://www.sunbelt-software.com/product.cfm?id=945</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Product: Sunbelt Network Security Inspector</title><description>Sunbelt Network Security Inspector. Close the door on hackers! You have to find vulnerabilities before they become problems. SNSI is a low-cost, quick-install, fast- result vulnerability scanner that uses a top quality, commercial- grade database of ranked vulnerabilities for Windows networks. It's got great reports and shows how to plug holes fast and easy. Scan by single IP or IP-range, Ports, or Service. Multiplatform – SNSI can now scan Linux, SUSE, Solaris, HP UX, Cisco Routers, and HP Printers. Download your eval copy and test it in your own environment. </description><link>http://www.sunbelt-software.com/product.cfm?id=987</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Product: File Rescue Plus</title><description>File Rescue Plus. Oops - you've accidentally deleted the file that contains key data that you need right away! You've lost all the pictures you just downloaded from your digital camera! What do you do? Just run File Rescue Plus! Simply scan the disk and choose the files you want to recover. It's that simple!</description><link>http://www.sunbelt-software.com/product.cfm?id=390</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2004 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Product: iHateSpam for Exchange</title><description>iHateSpam for Exchange. IS SPAM NEGATIVELY AFFECTING ENTERPRISE PRODUCTIVITY AND SECURITY? iHateSpam for Exchange was uniquely developed for you: the Exchange Admin. Control spam according to the needs of your company, your users and especially your own needs! iHateSpam for Exchange (V5.5, 2000 and 2003) is an easy install and up and running in minutes. It is now the best-selling anti-spam solution for Exchange with more than 3,000 licenses in production sites. Test it in your own environment for 30 spam-free days. Download your eval copy now.</description><link>http://www.sunbelt-software.com/product.cfm?id=931</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2003 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Product: LanHound</title><description>LanHound. Low Cost, Powerful Network Protocol Analyzer and Monitor. Usable for switched networks!</description><link>http://www.sunbelt-software.com/product.cfm?id=925</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2003 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Product: PestPatrol Corporate Edition</title><description>PestPatrol Corporate Edition. PestPatrol is a powerful anti-hacker utility that finds and eliminates hacker tools, spyware and trojans from your personal computer or corporate network.</description><link>http://www.sunbelt-software.com/product.cfm?id=912</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2003 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>
